

Abdallah Safan

UNDERGRADUATE ENGINEER

CONTACT

P +201289090397

E abdallahsafan05@gmail.com

EDUCATION

Undergraduate Computer engineer -Cairo University - Faculty of Engineering

First year student grades in past year: A+

HONORS&AWARDS

intel isef medal 2018 **3** MOS in PowerPoint 2010

SUMMARY

I am an undergraduate computer engineer, having experience in various fields like Abstract science, Programming, Embedded systems and Microsoft office suit which I am certified in as Microsoft office specialist also I have 3 languages Arabic (mother tongue), English (c1 level) and French (b1 level) also I have work experience as a presentation designer and photomath expert.

EXPERIENCE

Photomath Expert

August 2022 - Present

- Helping students around the world to solve math problems using the Photomath app.
- Experienced in Algebra, Calculus, and Geometry.

Presentation Designer Freelancer,

January 2021 - January 2022

- Designed and developed professional presentations for clients in various needs.
- Collaborated with clients to understand their needs and tailor presentations to their preferences.
- - Managed multiple projects and met tight deadlines.

Sharing in Alabakera TV show

November 2020 - January 2021

IEEE embedded systems instructor

Jan 2024- present

SKILLS

- Microsoft Office Suite (PowerPoint, ______ Word, Excel)
- Excellent communication skills in English (C1 level)

Communication

QUERY writing

- Intermediate level in C++
- Intermediate level in OOP